BRAC Additional Records 5488 C
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 75-100-end (Box 8)
  - Labor Organizations - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Labor Organizations - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Labor Organizations - Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers, and Helpers International Union, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Labor Organizations - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers of the United States and Canada, 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Labor Organizations - Journeymen Stone Cutters Association of North America, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Labor Organizations - Utility Workers Union of America, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Labor Organizations - International Woodworkers of America, 1963-1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Labor Organizations - Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, 1963-1969 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Labor Organizations - International Association of Fire Fighters, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Labor Organizations - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Labor Organizations - Service and Maintenance Employees Union, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Labor Organizations - International Union of Operating Engineers, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Labor Organizations - International Union of Operating Engineers, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Labor Organizations - Hospital and Institutional Workers' union, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- 205 - 0 (Box 9)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - General, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    July 1, 1967-November 26, 1969
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - General, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    May 1, 1966-June 30, 1967
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - General, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    October 1, 1965-April 30, 1966
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - General, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    January 1-September 30, 1965
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Committee of Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations (Applying Awards), 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    1962-June 30, 1965
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Weekly Legislative Report, 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Special File: National Railroad Adjustment Board Exchange of Constitutions and Membership Applications, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Switch List, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Special File on Anti-Labor Legislation, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Committee of Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations (Applying Awards), 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    July 1, 1965-July 8, 1968
- 1, 2 (Box 10)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Assessments, 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    January 1, 1966-April 1, 1970
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    June-August 1969
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    January-May 1969
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    August-December 1967
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    March-July 1967
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    January-February 1967
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    October-December 1966
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    June-September 1966
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    March-May 1966
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    January-February 1966
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    September-December 1968
- 2, 3, 4, 6, 7; 206 - 31 (Box 11)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    January-March 1968
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Press Releases, 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    January 1, 1964-March 19, 1970
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Financial Statements, 1966-1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    January 1, 1966-September 2, 1969
  - District Councils - By-Laws - Milwaukee District Council, 1936-1958 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Public Relations, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    January 1, 1963-December 31, 1964
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Public Relations, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    January 1, 1963-December 31, 1964. Package.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Public Relations, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    January-July 1965
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Facts Sheets, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    January 1, 1960-March 20, 1967
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Minutes, Meetings, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    April-August 1968
- 210 - 0; 211 - 29 (Box 12)
  - Alabama State Federation of Labor, 1921-1959 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - State Commissions - Railroad, Utility, Labor, 1960-1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    January 1, 1960-May 18, 1971
  - State Commissions - Railroad, Utility, Labor - California Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - State Commissions - Railroad, Utility, Labor - New York State Labor Department, 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - State Federation of Labor - Arizona, 1932-1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - State Federation of Labor - Arkansas, 1934-1967 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - State Federation of Labor - California, 1962-1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    January 1, 1962-December 16, 1971
  - State Federation of Labor - Colorado, 1962-1969 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - State Federation of Labor - Connecticut, 1935-1965 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - State Federation of Labor - Delaware, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - State Federation of Labor - Florida, 1949-1967 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - State Federation of Labor - Georgia, 1933-1966 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - State Federation of Labor - Illinois, 1961-1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - State Federation of Labor - Indiana, 1921-1967 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Includes Newspaper
  - State Federation of Labor - Iowa, 1964-1966 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - State Federation of Labor - Kansas, 1964-1971 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - State Federation of Labor - Kentucky, 1933-1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - State Federation of Labor - Maine, 1923-1966 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - LABOR Newspaper, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    June 1966
  - Journal of Proceedings of the Fifth Biennial Convention - Maine State Federated Labor Council, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    June 17-19, 1964. Bound.
  - State Federation of Labor - Maryland, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - State Federation of Labor - Louisiana, 1958-1971 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - State Federation of Labor - Massachusetts, 1936-1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - State Federation of Labor - Michigan, 1924-1965 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - State Federation of Labor - Minnesota, 1930-1963 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - State Federation of Labor - Mississippi, 1922-1965 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - State Federation of Labor - Missouri, 1950-1967 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - State Federation of Labor - Montana, 1938-1972 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - State Federation of Labor - Nebraska, 1929-1963 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - State Federation of Labor - New Hampshire, 1947-1965 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - State Federation of Labor - New Jersey, 1960-1967 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - State Federation of Labor - New Mexico, 1960-1967 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- 30; 213 - 57 (Box 13)
  - Newfoundland Federation of Labor, 1955-1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - State Federation of Labor- New York, 1960-1965 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - State Federation of Labor - North Carolina, 1960-1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - State Federation of Labor - North Dakota, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - State Federation of Labor - Ohio, 1961-1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - State Federation of Labor - Oklahoma, 1923-1965 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - State Federation of Labor - Oregon, 1937-1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - State Federation of Labor - Pennsylvania, 1960-1965 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - State Federation of Labor - Rhode Island, 1956-1962 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - State Federation of Labor - South Carolina, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - State Federation of Labor - Tennessee, 1934-1964 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - State Federation of Labor - Texas, 1925-1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - State Federation of Labor - Utah, 1942-1970 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - State Federation of Labor - Vermont, 1925-1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - State Federation of Labor - Virginia, 1939-1965 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - State Federation of Labor - Washington, 1960-1971 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - State Federation of Labor - West Virginia, 1923-1961 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - State Federation of Labor - Wisconsin, 1959-1961 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - State Federation of Labor - Wyoming, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - City Central Bodies - Asheville, North Carolina, 1965-1969 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - City Central Bodies - Atlanta, Georgia, 1929-1962 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - City Central Bodies - Chicago, Illinois, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - City Central Bodies - Cleveland, Ohio, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - City Central Bodies - Denver, Colorado, 1929-1961 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - City Central Bodies - Knoxville, Tennessee, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - City Central Bodies - Louisville, Kentucky, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - City Central Bodies - Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - City Central Bodies - New York City, New York, 1921-1963 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - City Central Bodies - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - City Central Bodies - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - City Central Bodies - Washington, District of Columbia, 1921-1962 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - City Central Bodies - Winston-Salem Central Labor Union, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Jurisdiction - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1951-1959 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Jurisdiction - International Longshoremen's Association (Port Tampa, Florida), 1937-1960 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Jurisdiction - International Longshoremen's Association, 1938-1958 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Jurisdiction - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1958-1969 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Jurisdiction - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (Merchandise Services, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada), 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Jurisdiction - Transportation-Communication Employees Union (Chesapeake and Ohio), 1966-1971 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    March 1, 1966-March 29, 1971
  - Jurisdiction - Transportation-Communication Employees Union, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    July 1, 1967-September 30, 1968
- 57 (cont.)-32; 214 - 0-13; 215 - 0-3 (Box 14)
  - Transportation-Communication Employees Union (Chesapeake and Ohio) - February 1966 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Transportation-Communication Employees Union - 10/1/66-6/30/67 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Transportation-Communication Employees Union - 1965-9/30/1966 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - January 1960: Brotherhood Maintenance, Building Service Employees, International Association of Machinists, Catholic Welfare Conference (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1/1/65: National Council of the Churches of Christ USA and 1964: Moral Rearmament (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1956: Religious Action in the Social and Civic Order (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Religion and Labor Council of America (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 1959: YMCA Transportation Department (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 1962: National Religion and Labor Council of America (Canada) and 1960: John A. Ryan Forum (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 1/1/65: General Charitable Organizations (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 1962: National Council of Senior Citizens, Inc. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - August 1949: American Heritage Foundation (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 1/1/1963: The Arthritis Foundation (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 1/1/1961: American Cancer Society (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 1957: Canadian Cancer Society (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Telegraph Equipment Information and Agreements (Box 14, Folder 16)
- 4-end; 216 - 0-4 (Box 15)
  - Charitable Organizations - Cancer Institute, Eleanor Roosevelt, 1959-1964 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Charitable Organizations - Community Chest (United Appeal), 1961-1970 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Charitable Organizations - Father Flanagan's Boys Town, 1949-1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Charitable Organizations - American Heart Association, 1963-1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Charitable Organizations - American Red Cross, 1964-1970 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Charitable Organizations - Canadian Red Cross, 1953-1962 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Charitable Organizations - American Federation of the Physically Handicapped, 1956-1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Charitable Organizations - National Federation of the Blind, 1945-1960 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Charitable Organizations - Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial Commission, 1962-1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Charitable Organizations - Children's Hospital (George M. Harrison), 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Charitable Organizations - Children's Asthma Research Institute and Hospital Fund (CARIH), 1968-1971 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Educational Programs, Universities - General, 1967-1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    January 1, 1967-December 1972. Includes Bound Materials
  - Educational Programs - Harvard University, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    January 1, 1970-January 1, 1973
  - Educational Programs - Harvard University, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    January 1, 1967-Decemebr 30, 1969
  - Educational Programs - Princeton University, 1960-1967 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    May 1, 1960-November 13, 1967. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Educational Programs - Radio Broadcasts - Pearson, 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - A Guide to Hawaii - Public Employee Collective Bargaining (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Education - Radio Broadcast - Pearson, 1953-1968 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- 5-end; 217 - 0-4 (Box 16)
  - Education - Universities - Roosevelt University, 1958-1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Education - Universities - Columbia University, 1960-1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Education - Universities - American University, 1963-1970 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Educational Programs - University of Minnesota, 1960-1967 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Coronary Heart Disease Among Railroad Employees in the United States, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    March 2, 1966.
  - Education Programs - Universities - Afro-Asian Institute for Labour Studies and Cooperation in Israel, 1964-1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Educational Programs - University of Chicago, 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Latin American Trade Union Project; The American Institute for Free Labor Development. Includes bound material.
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development - Social Projects Department Budget, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development - Education Department Budget, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Universities - University of Puerto Rico, 1961-1968 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Education - Universities - University of Cincinnati, 1958-1962 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Educational Programs - Universities - Labour College of Canada, 1963-1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - International Affairs - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1961-1968 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - International Affairs - United States Committee for Refugees, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - International Labour Conference - Fiftieth Session, Report 3, Part 2 - Third Item on the Agenda: Information and Reports on the Application of Conventions and Recommendations, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Bound.
  - International Affairs - United Nations - GMH Member, Board of Directors, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - International Affairs - United Nations Association of the United States - National Citizens' Commission of International Cooperation, 1965-1968 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Includes Bound Materials. 1965-June 30, 1968
  - International Affairs - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1950-1962 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- 5-end (Box 17)
  - International Affairs - International Transport Workers Federation, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    September 1971-June 1973
  - International Affairs - International Transport Workers Federation, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    June 28, 1968-August 31, 1971
  - International Affairs - International Transport Workers' Federation, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    January 1, 1964-June 18, 1968. Includes Bound Materials.
  - International Affairs - Coordinating Council of Organizations on International Trade Policy, 1962-1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - International Affairs - General, 1963-1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    January 1, 1963-November 1972. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Export-Import Bank of Washington - Report to the Congress, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    July-December 1964. Bound.
  - International Affairs - Citizens Committee for International Development (George M. Harrison, Member), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - International Affairs Department, Foreign Relations - Trade Union Exchange Program, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    February 1970
  - International Affairs - Cincinnati Council on World Affairs (George M. Harrison, Member of Advisory Board), 1961-1965 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- 218 - 229-end (Box 18)
  - Foreign Organizations - Britain and Ireland, Salaried Staff of Transport (Clerks Railway: Great Britain and Ireland), 1931-1959 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Organizations - British Railway Unions, 1929-1958 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Organizations - British Trades Union Congress, 1922-1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Organizations - Israel, National Committee for American Trade Union Council (Histadrut) - American Freedom Forest Dedication, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Negro Organizations - Negro Labor Committee, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Negro Organizations - National Negro Labor Council, 1951-1964 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Negro Organizations - Negro American Labor Council, 1960-1966 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Negro Organizations - National Trade Union Conference for Negro Rights (Railway Labor Executives' Association Negro), 1950 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League, 1959-1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    December 1959-March 1970. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Newspaper - General, 1965-1969 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Labor Newspaper - Financial Statements, 1965-1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Labor Newspaper - Lodge Subscriptions, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    September-October 1965
  - Labor Newspaper - Annual and Special Meetings, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Who's Who - General (International; In America; In Railroad; In the Midwest), 1960-1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - History of Labor - General, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - District Councils - Detroit, 1960-1965 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - District Councils - Kansas City - Springfield Joint Council of Lodges, 1957-1961 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - District Councils - Minneapolis Joint Council, 1960-1970 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - District Councils - Philadelphia, 1938-1959 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - The John Fitzgerald Kennedy Library Corporation (George M. Harrison, Trustee), 1964-1966 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Harry S. Truman Library, 1954-1963 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    July 1954-February 25, 1963. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Death Benefit Department - Claims, 1962-1970 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Employer's Tax Guide - Circular E (New Social Security Tax and New Withholding Allowances), 1967 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    January 1967. Bound.
  - Death Benefit Department - Claims (Transportations Communication International Union - TCU), 1969 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Death Benefit Department - General (Transportation Communication International Union - TCU), 1969 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Death Benefit Department - General, 1935-1968 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Death Benefit Department - Actuarial Investigation, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Death Benefit Department - Actuarial Investigation, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Death Benefit Department - Actuarial Investigation, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Death Benefit Department - Actuarial Investigation, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Death Benefit Department - Actuarial Investigation and Report on the Second Valuation of Liabilities Under and Assets of the Railway Clerks Staff Retirement Plan, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Death Benefits Department - Special File (Office of Labor Management and Welfare-Pension Reports, United States Department of Labor), 1962-1969 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- 224-225 - 250-504 (Box 19)
  - District Councils - Chicago, 1963-1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Death Benefit Department - General, 1957-1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Includes Pamphlets
  - Employment - Grand Lodge, 1968-1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    January 1, 1968-June 30, 1973
  - Lodges - General, 1960-1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    April 1, 1960-December 31, 1970
  - Lodge 1203 - General, 1947-1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 1226 - General, 1949-1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 3058 - General, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    March 1974-September 1975
  - American Arbitration Association - General, 1965-1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Congress of Railway Unions - Financial Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    January 1970-March 1974
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago and Western Lake District (Express), 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    January 19, 1965-December 31, 1966. Includes Bound Materials
  - Boards of Adjustment - Express Division, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    December 18, 1975-January 21, 1976
- 230 - 4-150 (Box 20)
  - Organizations - Canadian Pacific Railroad, 1945-1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Organizations - Canadian Pacific Railway (Merchandise Service), 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Representation - Des Moines Union Railway Company - Application for Certification as Bargaining Agent of Three Employees, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Grand Trunk Western Railway - Representation Dispute, 1958-1961 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Organizations - Great Northern, 1945-1968 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Organizations - Houston Belt and Terminal, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Organizations - Missouri Pacific (Gulf District), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Organizations - Kansas City Southern, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Organizations - Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Company, 1955-1960 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Organizations - Pennsylvania Railroad - Application from the Seafarers' International Union of North America to Investigate a Representation Dispute, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Dispute between Marine Tug Dispatchers and Assistant Marine Tug Dispatchers
  - Organizations - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie - Mediation Case: Application for the Services of the Board to Investigate a Representation Dispute, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Dispute between Station Masters and Assistant Station Masters Employed by the Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Company
  - Organizations - Gulf, Colorado, and Santa Fe Hospital Association (Temple, Texas), 1957-1962 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Organizations - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Organizations - Southern Pacific (Pacific System), 1950-1962 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    May 2, 1950-August 1962
  - Organizations - Southern Pacific (Pacific System), 1962-1970 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    September 6, 1962-June 15, 1970
  - Organizations - Southern Pacific Transport Company, 1948-1964 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    1948-September 10, 1964
  - Organizations - Texas and Pacific Railway, 1955-1970 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    1955-June 11, 1970